summersearch.net 2017-07-06

# Privacy Policy - Summer Search

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for Summer Search. Summer Search knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy and applies to all information received by Summer Search, both online and offline, on any Platform ('Platform' includes the Summer Search website and mobile applications), as well as any electronic, written or oral communications.

**Information Collection and Use**  
Summer Search will not sell, share, trade or rent email addresses or other personal information with any entity, nor send mailings to our constituents on behalf of other organizations, in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Summer Search collects information from our users in a variety of ways through our website and email messages. We reserve the right to disclose personally identifiable information as may be required by law; to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or other legal process; if we determine that such disclosure is necessary to assert or protect our legal rights or property, or to protect the legal rights or property of others; to prevent harm to any person; or in connection with an actual or proposed merger or other transaction or proceeding involving a transfer of all or part of the programs or assets to which the information pertains. We also reserve the right to disclose personal information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Summer Search's Terms and Conditions or other agreements, or as otherwise required or permitted by law.

****Website Donor Privacy**  
** Credit card transactions on the Summer Search website are processed by Authorize.net. Authorize.net collects information on behalf of Summer Search and does not disclose it to any party other than Summer Search. Our donors' information will only be used for purposes necessary to process the donation.  Authorize.net (a subsidiary of Cybersource Corporation) uses security measures to protect all personal information with physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards; sophisticated security monitoring tools; documented security policies; use of strong encryption for credit card information, and restricted access of personally identifiable information. The transactions are governed by Authorize.net’s privacy policy. **  
**

**Cookies**  
Summer Search uses cookies to remember if users have logged in while on our site. This allows web site users to avoid logging in more than once, thereby saving time. Users have the option of disabling or not accepting cookies by changing the preferences on their browsers. If users opt to disable cookies, they will still be able to use our Web site. However, they may lose some functionality or the ability to post to the message boards. No personally identifiable information (e-mail address, name, etc.) is collected with the cookies being utilized. Accepting cookies while on the Summer Search site will not put the user at risk for marketing to third parties or affiliates as we are the sole owners of the information collected on this site.

**Web Statistics**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use for reporting and sponsorship purposes. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Sharing**  
We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners, sponsors, and donors. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Summer Search does not claim any responsibility for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Security**  
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information, and we have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

**Surveys**  
Occasionally, Summer Search requests information from users via Web surveys. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information.

**Web Site Registration**  
In order to use some features of this Web site, users must first complete the registration form. During registration, users are required to give their contact information. This information is used to contact users about Summer Search and the topics on our site for which they have expressed interest and to enable users to retrieve lost passwords. This information is captured into a Salesforce.com database. Salesforce.com will not review, share, distribute, or reference any such Customer Data except as provided in the salesforce.com Master Subscription Agreement, or as may be required by law.

**Updating Personal Information**  
If a user's personal contact information changes or if a user no longer desires to be a part of our web community we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update, or remove that the personal data that was provided to us. There are several ways users can make these changes:

  * Use the "Edit My Profile" link from their homepage
  * E-mail info@summersearch.org or call 415-362-5225 to change, correct, or remove information

**Newsletter and Other Email Communications**  
Summer Search may communicate with you by sending electronic newsletters, invitations or other email notices. These services are provided by Blackbaud NetCommunity and are governed by Blackbaud NetCommunity’s privacy policy. Summer Search will only send these messages to you if you have expressed an interest in the organization. If you received a message in error, or no longer wish to receive communications from Summer Search, you may optout of future mailings by selecting “unsubscribe” at the bottom of each message. If users elect to use our "Send This to a Friend" function, we ask them for the friend's email address. Summer Search will automatically send friends a one-time e-mail message inviting them to visit the site. Summer Search stores this information temporarily for the sole purpose of sending this one-time message.

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our home page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

**Questions**  
Questions regarding the Summer Search privacy policy should be directed to:

Summer Search  
101 Howard Street, Suite 250  
San Francisco, CA 94105  
info[@summersearch.org](mailto:supportcenter@summersearch.org)
